我要去一趟洗手间 很快回来
Hey, I'm gonna go to the bathroom real quick.
我想去照照镜子
I want to look in the mirror
确认下我的眼神依旧死气沉沉
and make sure I'm still dead in the eyes.
你觉得你能应付好我这区吗
You think you can handle my section?
当然 我觉得我完全应付得过来
Uh, yeah, I think I can handle it.
厄尔 不知道你有没有注意到
Hey, Earl, I don't know if you noticed,
但现在整间餐厅都归我管耶
but I'm running the whole diner right now.
厉害吧
What, what?
十号桌的客人好像噎着了
The customer at table ten appears to be choking,
我想去帮忙
And I would help,
但我上次对一个白人女性实施海姆利克法
but the last time I gave a white woman the heimlich,
被抓进伯明翰的监狱关了六个月呢
I did six months in the Birmingham city jail.
天啊 您是噎着了吗
Oh, my God, are you choking?
天啊 我感觉您像是噎着了
Oh, my god, I feel like you're choking!
这里有人是医生吗
Is anyone here a doctor?
我在胡说什么 这里哪会有医生来
What am I saying? I forgot where I am.
这里有人看过《实习医生风云》吗
Has anyone here ever seen Scrubs?
当有姑娘噎着时该怎么做啊
What do you do when a girl is choking?
我会从她嘴里"拔出来"一点
I just back up a few inches.
我们该怎么办
What do we do?
怎么办啊 这个女人被噎着了
What do we do? This woman is choking!
非常感谢
Thank you so much.
不用客气
You're welcome.
你觉得自己的命值多少 就给多少小费吧
And feel free to tip me what you think your life's worth.
感觉要有三块钱入袋啦
I feel 3 bucks coming my way.
上菜啦 各位 这家店就我一个服务员
Here you go, guys. I'm the only waitress.
您等这汉堡的时间
Sorry you waited longer for the burger
比科斯比毛衣再流行还久 真对不住
than you did for that Cosby sweater to come back.
麦克斯 看我的表情 我非常不爽
Max, look at my face. I'm very upset.
原来是不爽啊 我还以为你是一脸便秘相呢
Is that what that means? I just assumed you were constipated.
卡洛琳又迟到了
Caroline is late again.
她最好别再拿你们新蛋糕店当借口
And she better not use your new cupcake shop as an excuse this time,
因为妹子 老娘才不信那屁话呢
'cause sister, that crap ain't gonna fly.
首先
First of all,
请不要学黑人疯婆子电影里的语气说话
stop talking like you're in a Tyler Perry movie.
其次
And secondly,
卡洛琳在呢 她在厨房啊
Caroline's here; she's in the kitchen.
是吗 刚才我在厨房
Oh, really? 'cause when I was in there,
你跟我说她在外面
you told me she was out here.
你耍老娘啊
You play me, fool.
请别学黑人疯婆子电影续集里的语气说话
Stop talking like you're in a Tyler Perry Sequel.
-其次... -我问厄尔好了
- And secondly-- - I'll ask Earl.
厄尔
Earl...
哎哟喂
Ow!
怎么了 你干嘛尖叫
What happened? Why did you scream?
我刚不小心坐到我的"蛋"了
I accidentally sat on one of my boys!
你今晚有见过卡洛琳吗
Have you seen Caroline tonight?
当然有啦 兄弟
Of course I have, man.
我刚看见她走到那头去洗手间了
I just saw her go down the hall to the ladies room.
瞧 开心了吧
There. Happy?
你破解了大谜题 小洛克·福尔小厮
You've solved the big mystery, Shortlock Holmes.
慢着 她没有端任何她的...
Wait, she didn't pick up any of her--
卡洛琳
Caroline?
没功夫搭理你 阿憨
Can't talk now, Han.
我得跟你说多少遍 你才愿意
And how many more times do I have to ask you
修好这个放派的转盘啊
to fix this damn pie carousel?
温度一点都不够凉
I mean, the temp just isn't cool enough,
西米露很容易会变质
and those tapiocas are gonna turn bad.
如果你想吃官司 就继续忽视我的话吧
If you do want a lawsuit, just keep ignoring me.
麦克斯 能进我几分钟前
Max, can I see you in the kitchen
就待过的厨房说说话吗
where I was just a couple minutes ago
虽然我后来去上了个厕所
after I got out of the ladies room?
对啊 赶紧弄那玩意的温度
Yeah, get on that temperature thing.
里面霉菌那个多呀
There's so much mold growing in there
樱桃派都得来个子宫颈抹片检查了
that cherry pie's gonna need a pap smear.
刚才还真是有种够胆
That was some ballsy, bold,
牛逼哄哄的扯谎呀
in-your-face awesome lying.
虎父无犬子嘛 父亲大人
I learned it by watching you, dad.
不撒谎不行 为了蛋糕店
Had to lie. We need every minute
我们得尽可能偷时间 能偷多少是多少
we can steal away from here to get the cupcake shop ready.
我们还得再刷一遍漆
We still have to do the second coat of paint,
搞定桌椅...
figure out tables and chairs...
看什么 我没时间吃午饭
What? Didn't have time for lunch.
我又不在乎
Oh, I don't care.
我只是惊讶你居然还用勺子
I'm surprised you're using a spoon.
我通常直接把脸埋进去吃
I just stick my face in it.
我有个能把这一切搞定的绝妙主意
So, my brilliant idea of how we get this all done
就是招个实习生来帮忙
is we should get an intern to help.
什么 不行
What? No.
我当不了用实习生的老板
I can't be a person that has an intern.
我连当个没实习生跟班的老板都很勉强了
I can barely be a person that doesn't have an intern.
麦克斯 所有企业都用实习生啊
Max, all businesses use interns.
只需在纽约大学或哥伦比亚大学的网上
We just have to post an ad online
发个招聘广告
at NYU or Columbia,
就能收到雪片般飞来
And we'll have 20 applicants battling it out
争先恐后求这苦差事的申请
to do our grunt work for credit.
被你说得像是《饥饿游戏之大学版》
You make it sound like The Hunger Games: college edition.
抱歉 我反对不给钱让人干白活
Sorry, I'm against getting people to work for free.
我同意 麦克斯
I'm with you, Max.
我们黑人免费"实习"了436年呢[黑奴]
My people were interns for 436 years.
我才刚习惯拥有自己的小生意这个念头
I am just getting used to the idea of having my own business
现在你就要我当别人的老板啊
and now you want me to be someone's boss?
我不是当老板的料
I am not the boss.
我是那种在老板背后说他坏话的人
I'm the person who talks behind the boss's back.
上菜
Pick up.
谢了 阿憨是个傻逼吧
Thanks. Isn't han a tool?
-纯傻逼 -一个小傻逼[工具]
- Total tool. - Yeah, a tiny tool.
就像拿来修眼镜的小工具一样
Like the kind you fix your eyeglasses with.
看见了吗
See?
那才是我擅长的事
That's my wheelhouse.
我不想让人来免费帮咱们工作
Look, I don't want to ask someone to work for free.
我们可以自己做啊
We can do it all ourselves.
你想一切都自己搞定吗 没问题
You want to do it all yourself? Great.
我会列个待办清单 你得去办好一切
I'll write everything you need to do on a to-do list.
为什么你不"去办"呢
Why don't you to-do that?
然后我"去把它撕成碎片"
And I will to-tear it up.
我们要把什么撕碎
What're we tearing up?
如果是卡洛琳的翘臀 那我已经搞定了
'cause if it's that ass, I already got that covered.
安迪 那番话真是又甜蜜又下流
Hi, Andy. That's so sweet and dirty.
要这么激情吗 你又不是要被送去打仗
Easy, easy. What are you, shipping off to war?
来 这大包彩虹糖给你
Here. Take this giant bag of skittles
-别插手这事 -老娘可没这么好哄
- and look the other way. - I'm not that easy.
哇 新的神秘口味
Ooh, new mystery flavors?
下班后再见对吧
We getting together after you get off work?
今天会非常晚
It'll be really late.
我和麦克斯还得去小蛋糕店
Max and I still have to go to the cupcake shop
用胶带把窗户粘上 这样明天好开工装修
and tape up the windows so we can start the trim tomorrow.
好吧 虽然我不擅长刷漆
Okay, I'm not very good at painting,
但你刷漆时 我可以在一边做这个
but I can do this while you paint.
对
Yeah.
就这样 把油漆刷到墙上
Yeah, roll that paint on that wall.
你真是可爱到爆
You are so freaking cute.
白人果然都是白痴
Ugh, white people.
你们何不找个实习生呢
Look, why don't you guys just get an intern?
我当初开店的时候也是这么做
That's what I did when I opened my shop.
你们俩简直就是魔鬼军阀
You two are like evil warlords
开采着无辜丧尸的灵魂
mining the souls of innocent zombies.
对了 要注意看看你的店
Oh, and keep your eyes peeled at your store.
门卫说他发现里面有老鼠屎
The janitor told me he saw some rat droppings.
不过你们只需弄几个扑鼠器就行了
But all you gotta do is set up some traps.
真恶心 谁来干这活啊
Oh, gross. Who's gonna do that?
实习生吗
The intern?
露丝 纽约大学大二生 主修金融是吗
So, Ruth, you are a sophomore at NYU, majoring in finance?
你知道是无偿干白活吧
You know you're not gonna get paid.
一分钱都没有哦
No money at all.
对啊 实习就是这样啊
Yup, it's in internship.
我是说 没关系的 对吧
I mean, it's all good, right?
直到你需要钱就有关系了
It's all good until you need money.
我们是家刚起步的公司
Well, we're a startup company,
刚开设我们头一家零售店
and we're launching our very first retail store,
所以你需要负责很多小事
so there's a lot of details that you'll be responsible for.
很多搬运工的事
There's a lot of carrying things,
可能还有些捕猎的事情哦
maybe some trapping things.
没关系 我有车
Oh, it's cool. I have a car.
你是有车一族 居然还想当实习生
You have a car and you want to be an intern?
不然咱俩换一换
How 'bout if we switch places?
我来当有车的实习生
I'll be the intern with the car,
你来坐这张烂的折叠椅
and you can sit on a broken folding chair
坐在女版唐纳德·川普[大亨]的旁边
next to Donna Trump over here.
我和麦克斯现在得开个小会
Well, Max and I need to have a little meeting right now,
你最好去那边的等候区稍等一会
so if you could go over to the waiting room, that'd be great.
可以吗 露丝[同情心]
Okay, Ruth?
我想说我知道我的名字很奇怪
I just wanna say I know my name is weird,
但现在改名太晚了 对吧
but like it's too late, right?
麦克斯 你干嘛试图说服她
Max, why are you trying to convince her
不要当我们的实习生啊
to not be our intern?
你又干嘛不告诉她
Why are you not saying,
"你可能因老鼠而染上狂犬病和黑死病啊"
"You may get rabies and bubonic plague from our rats?"
别提老鼠
Don't mention the rats.
你会吓跑人家
You're chasing them away.
而且我们这里只有老鼠屎 没有老鼠
And we do not have rats. We have rat droppings.
别过早下结论
Let's not jump to conclusions.
你说得对 老鼠可能只是
You're right, the rats are probably
来这里借个厕所而已
just coming in here to use the bathroom.
我们需要一名实习生
Look, we need an intern.
目前为止 你最喜欢哪一个
Now, who do you like so far?
大咪咪的那个
The one with the big boobs.
我就知道 你们大咪咪星人都相互帮助
I knew it. All you big boob people stick together.
姑娘们
Hi, girls.
你们是在举行选美比赛吗 没邀请我
Are you having a beauty contest and didn't invite me
是为了给其他姑娘一个机会吧
to give the other girls a chance?
我们是在面试实习生
We're interviewing people to be our intern.
没钱拿哦
Who doesn't get paid.
这是给你们的
Well, this is for you.
真的不必了
You didn't have to do that.
你都给我们开店的钱了
You already gave us the money for the shop.
我知道 我就是人太好了
I know, I'm too wonderful.
但这是求好运的
But it's for good luck,
而且你们可能会很需要好运
and sounds like you're gonna need it.
奥列格说这一带是老鼠的中央车站
Oleg says that it's rat central station around here.
没老鼠 苏菲 不过是几颗老鼠屎而已
Not rats, Sophie, just rat droppings.
几颗老鼠屎啊
Oh, just rat droppings.
好吧 那就没问题了
Oh, okay, no problem there.
你上气不接下气
Are you out of breath
是因为你是从1974年跑过来的吗
because you jogged here all the way from 1974?
很性感吧
Sexy, huh?
你们真应该看看他慢跑时的小翘臀
You should see his badunkadunk when he jogs.
东西给你拿来了 60个扑鼠器
Well, here they are. 60 rat traps.
姑娘们
Girls...
我不想插手你们的生意
I don't want to interfere with your business,
但这到底是怎么回事
but what the hell is goin' on here?
这里没有好看的桌子 也没有漂亮的椅子
There's no fancy tables or pretty chairs.
这里毫无吸引力
I mean, this place is so unappealing,
连我都不艳惊四座了
even I don't look good here.
别担心
No worries.
我们有些老派冰淇淋店的可爱桌椅
We have some adorable old-school ice cream tables and chairs
暂放在斯塔顿岛一个古怪有趣的垃圾场里
on hold at a kooky, fun staten island junkyard.
真不敢相信你居然面不改色地
I can't believe you didn't just shoot a blood clot
把垃圾堆家具形容得这么可爱
trying to make dump furniture sound cute.
好吧 姑娘们 等你们正式开门再打给我
Okay, girls, well, call me when you have a real business.
对了 我要把这个带走
Yeah, and I'm-I'm gonna take this,
以防老鼠在里面拉屎
you know, so that the rats don't poop in it.
走吧 小翘臀
Come on, badunkadunk.
对了 麦克斯
Oh, and, uh, Max...
她不错 真的
Oh, she's good. Yes.
我就知道 你们大咪咪星人都相互帮助
I knew it. All you big boob people stick together.
好了
Well?
终于到了这一刻
Here we are.
就剩最后三人了
The final three.
你知道我喜欢哪个 我给你个提示
Well, you know the one I like. I'll give you a clue.
左第一 右第二
One, two.
站在我面前的是两位美丽
Standing in front of me I see two beautiful,
条件良好的年轻女性
qualified young women.
她现在是要学《全美超模大赛》那套吗
Is she really going all Top Model right now?
是就好了 人家是给钱的
If only. They pay.
我退出 泰拉[超模主持人]
I'm out, Tyra.
露丝 恭喜你
Ruth, congratulations.
你被选为我们的实习生
You've been selected to be our intern.
麦克斯 你能让露丝开始干活吗
Max, will you get Ruth started on something?
对 我得到实习的机会了
Yup, I got the internship.
这样吧 我来弄
You know what? I got it.
又没花钱请你
It's not like you're getting paid.
大咪咪星人肯定更好说话
Big boob people are so much easier.
你小时候 是不是
As a kid, people told you
做什么屁事大家都称赞你啊
everything you did was amazing, didn't they?
那是通过赞赏来强化我的积极度
I was given a lot of positive reinforcement.
我觉得这也是我去年
I think it gave me the confidence
有信心撑过难关的原因
that's gotten me through this last year.
是时候告诉你真相了
Well, it's time you heard the truth.
你做啥事都很烂
You stink at stuff.
比如刷墙就很烂
Like painting.
行 你也做啥事都很烂啊
Fine. And you stink at stuff too.
连叫实习生做事这事都不会
Like telling an intern what to do.
露丝必须得去那演唱会嘛
Ruth had to go to that concert.
人家好早就买的票了
She had the tickets for weeks.
是她好友艾希莉D 艾希莉B的联合生日会呢
It was Ashley D and Ashley B's joint birthday. Duh.
所以实习生在大玩特玩
And so the intern's out having fun,
而我们这两位老板
and here we are, the bosses,
半夜三点来这刷墙
painting the walls at 3:00 A.M.
我是在刷墙啊
Well, I'm painting.
而你看起来像是自闭芭蕾舞者在犯二
You got a kind of autistic ballerina thing going on over there.
我能问你件事吗
Can I ask you something?
我不喜欢魔力红
I don't like Maroon 5.
你再问几次也一样
No matter how many times you ask,
不喜欢就是不喜欢
the answer will always be no.
不是要问这个
Not that.
你觉得我今晚让安迪别来我们家合适吗
Would it be okay if I told Andy not to come over tonight
我今天太累了
'cause I'm so exhausted,
还是你觉得才在一起不久 我就说
or is it a little too early in the relationship to be all,
"我今天没精力把双腿开到耳旁 任你..."
"I don't think I can have my legs up around my ears tonight"?
没事的
It's fine.
你觉得他就不会想要
You don't think he'd enjoy a night off
放一晚假 不用被魔力红魔音穿脑吗
from constant Maroon 5 badgering? He would.
太尴尬 算了
Feels awkward. Can't.
双腿开到耳后 任他... 没问题的啦
My legs can go up there. They're fine.
我还不想跟他说到这事
I don't want to have that conversation right now.
我懂你
Hey, look, I get it.
常有事情难以启齿 不想谈到
There are conversations you don't want to have.
例如 "露丝 这里是0圆薪水
Like, "Hey, Ruth, here's $0.
去把捕鼠夹放好"
Put down some rat traps."
那还完全没人去搞呢
We have a box right here that's not touched.
都说了你的性事部分已经谈完
Look, we're not talking about your relationship anymore.
别再说了
We're done.
别紧张嘛 不见得是大老鼠
Relax. It's probably not even a rat,
可能只是小小鼠辈 没事的
it's probably a mouse. Not a big deal.
妈呀 我的老天啊 我看到了 在那里
Oh, my God! Oh, my God, I see it! There it is!
-那小老鼠吗 -才不是小老鼠
- The mouse? - That is not a mouse!
那简直是有小老鼠开的车那么大
That is a car that a mouse drives!
天啊 你看到它在哪
Oh my God. Where did you see it?
刚是在中间 对吧
It was in the middle, right?
你干嘛那么小声
Why are you whispering?
我怕被他听见我
I don't want him to hear me.
你怎么知道是个"他"
How do you know it's a he?
他好像用眼神强奸了我
He looked at me kind of rapey.
那边 他跑到那玩意后面了
There! He just ran behind the thing!
-什么玩意 -那个玩意啊
- What thing? - That thing!
这个玩意吗
This thing? Waah!
怎么 你看见它了吗
What? Did you see it?
不确定
I don't think so.
哪能不确定 它背上有马鞍呢
Oh, you'd know so. It has a saddle.
天啊
Oh, my God.
他刚靠胡须的巨力把那门顶开了
He just opened the door with the strength of his whiskers.
他进了厨房 不见了
He's gone. He went into the kitchen.
我们该怎么办啊
Oh, what should we do?
要不要叫警察叔叔来
Should we call the cops?
他又没持枪
He doesn't have a gun.
咱们就赶紧闪人
Let's just get out of here.
然后明早让除害虫公司来搞吧
We'll call an exterminator in the morning.
晚了 他又回来了
Too late, he's coming back!
-他朝我们冲过来了 -他要来咬我了
- Aah! He's charging us! - He's gonna bite me!
可以停手了
Waah! You can stop now!
你把人家活活刷死了
You painted him to death.
我仿佛看到了你在巴尼百货大抢购的画面
I just got a glimpse of you at a Barneys sample sale.
血肉横飞 谁去清理啊
What a mess. Who's gonna clean that up?
实习生吧
The intern?
安迪...
Oh, Andy...
我知道 我龙精虎猛
I know. I'm good at this.
怎么了 又有老鼠吗
What? Is there another rat?
你干嘛啊
What are you doing?
我忘了安迪来了嘛
I forgot Andy was here!
而且你的浪叫跟杀人叫声如出一撤
And your sex voice is the same as your murder voice.
你还要在那边继续看啊
So are you just gonna stand there?
你是在邀请我"三人行"吗
Are you offering me a three-way?
看来要激化成为杂交派对了
Well, it looks like we're about to be a full-blown orgy.
都半夜两点了 会是谁啊
It's 2:00 A.M. Who could this be?
是露丝
It's Ruth.
-露丝 -对 我是不是来迟了
- Ruth? - Yes. I'm late, right?
她干嘛来啊
Why is she here?
我发短信告诉她你需要灌肠剂
I texted her and said you needed an enema.
这是高强度工业等级的姐妹私房话吧
Okay, now, this is some industrial-strength girl talk.
我得做出行动 让她知道谁主谁仆啊
I had to do something to show her who was boss.
我去康泰纳仕实习时学到的
I learned it while interning at Conde Nast.
我们实习生都帮人半夜买过灌肠剂
We've all gotten someone an enema in the middle of the night,
算是个"通过仪式"
it's a rite of passage.
帮助别人"通道"顺畅的仪式吗
For someone to get their passage right?
抢了我台词啊
Beat me to it.
到了 去开门吧
There. Go open the door.
你知道这非做不可
You know what has to happen.
麦克斯得让露丝干她的活
Max has to put Ruth in her place
她才有办法学着当个老板
so she can learn how to be a boss.
就这样啊 那就好
Oh. That's all? Good.
刚才听你语气
'Cause I thought from your tone,
我还以为你让她非做不可的是灌肠
you were gonna force Max to have an enema.
抱歉我来晚了
Sorry I'm late.
我吃了一小块大麻饼干 得停车打个小盹
I had the tiniest pot cookie and had to pull over to take a nap.
好了 这是你的灌肠剂 慢慢享用
Anyway, here is your enema. Enjoy.
他们只卖三合一包
They only had the triple pack.
等等 露丝
Wait, Ruth?
麦克斯有话想对你说
Max has something she wants to say to you.
麦克斯 你想对露丝说什么来着
Max, what did you want to say to Ruth?
谢谢你买的三合一包
Um, thanks for the triple?
三倍药量 三倍享受
Three times the fun.
你确定不要我帮忙吗
You sure you don't want me to help you with that?
不用 没事的
Oh, no, it's okay.
你把捕鼠夹都拿出箱子呢 需要休息一下
You took the rat traps out of the box, you need a break.
而且 小时候我家买不起捕鼠夹桌游
Plus, we couldn't afford the game mouse trap when I was a kid,
这是我能玩到最像的版本了
and this is the closest I'm gonna get.
那你打算什么时候烤小蛋糕啊
So, when do you make the cupcakes?
我可以现在就做啊
I guess I could make them now.
太好了 那我去喝个咖啡 好吧
Fun. I'll go get the coffees, right?
当然可以 没问题 随你吧
Sure, of course. Do whatever.
你有美好人生 我凭什么对你颐指气使
You got a life. Who am I to tell you what to do?
这是玛莎给我们的宣传文宣
Well, here's our Martha Stewart blurb,
放大印制
All blown up
准备好要摊开贴上墙了
and ready to roll out and paste up on that wall.
-露丝呢 -她在厨房里
- Where's Ruth? - She's in the kitchen.
-我刚从厨房出来 -那她是在厕所吧
- I was just in there. - Then she's in the bathroom.
天啊 你在把我当阿憨耍
Oh, my God, you're Haning me!
她去喝咖啡休息一下嘛
She took a coffee break.
什么 她才不需要休息
What? She didn't need a break.
她20分钟前才开工呢
She just started 20 minutes ago.
你的有钱人姿态又露出来了
Your rich is really coming out,
真是面目可憎啊
and it is not pretty.
忘了拿我手机了
Forgot my phone.
上紧发条啊 露丝 你们说是吧
I mean, get it together, Ruth, right?
看我示范 学着点
Watch and learn.
露丝 可以去把捕鼠夹放到店里每一个墙角吗
Ruth, can you put the rat traps down, one in each corner,
等你的实习工作弄完了 要喝咖啡再去
and then you can get coffee later after interning.
谢了
Thanks.
她挺傻逼的 对吧
She's kind of a tool, right?
-麦克斯 你刚说什么了吗 -没有啊
- Max, were you saying something? - Nope.
疼啊
Ouch!
对吧
Right?
你看这个笼子
Oh, look at this cage.
我妈以前在里面跳过舞吧[脱衣舞娘]
I think my mom used to dance in it.
就是这个
Here they are.
我让人家替我保留的就在这了
These are the ones I had the guy hold for us.
全套只需600块钱
Only $600 for all of them.
你觉得如何啊 干爹
What do ya think, daddy?
小美人 挺不错的 统统买了
I like 'em, doll. Wrap 'em up.
那干爹可以买点自己想要的东西吗
And can daddy get something he wants?
真可爱 放柜台上方吗
So cute. Over the counter?
这样就算我宿醉在店里打盹
And that way when I'm hungover and taking a nap,
人家也知道小蛋糕在哪卖
People can still find the cupcakes.
我们可以叫露丝把它擦干净
We could have Ruth clean it
然后让她粉刷这些并重换椅面
and then paint and reupholster these.
对了 她人呢
By the way, where is she?
她一个小时前就该到这里了
She was supposed to be here an hour ago.
发短信给她 查出她在哪
Text her and find out where she is.
你干嘛对人家身在何处 在干嘛有兴趣啊
Why are you so interested in where she is, what she's doing?
你是迷恋上人家了吗
Are you obsessed with her?
麦克斯 我又不是要扒她皮做皮包
Max, I don't want to make a purse out of her skin.
只是让她尽本分而已
I just want her to do her job.
算了 我来给她发短信吧
Never mind. I'll just text her.
小心点
Well, be careful.
别误删我珍藏的鸡鸡戴帽图
Don't delete any of my penis with a hat pictures.
就算误删了 也没什么损失啊
Even if I did, it's not a big deal.
奥列格随时乐意重拍
Oleg will always pose again.
但是我的感恩节小帽已经一去不返了
Yeah, but I'll never get that little pilgrim hat back.
你人在哪 你"昨天"就该到了
"WHERE ARE YOU? WE NEEDED YOU HERE YESTERDAY."
全大写 当老板的都是用全大写
All in caps, 'cause bosses talk in caps.
纯傻逼
Total tool.
你看
Look at that.
马上回短信 因为我是老板
Texted right back, 'cause I'm the boss.
她回...
She says...
她昨天太累了 她人不太舒服
Yesterday was super hard so she's not feeling great
所以她今天来不了
And she can't come in today?
我受够了 炒了她
That's it. She's fired.
给 你来负责炒她
Here. You have to fire her.
她都说她病了 你个康德那屎
She said she was sick, Conde nasty.
她才没病呢 只是看你好说话
She's not sick, she's just taking advantage
占你便宜 偷懒呢
'cause you're too friendly with her.
她是给我们打工的
She works for us.
对啊 免费干白活呢
Yeah, for free.
你怎么不干脆挖空人家
Why don't you just hollow her out
住进她身体里啊 你个禽兽老板
and live inside of her, you monster?
她好像是发错还是怎么着了
Um, I don't think we were supposed to get this.
"白痴的那个叫我去弄回垃圾家具
"The dumb one wants me to pick up all this crappy furniture.
对吧
Right?
我可能去吗
As if.
我十点会到酒吧 先帮我点杯贝里尼酒"
I'll be at the bar in ten. Order me a bellini."
她才是禽兽员工吧
Oh, who's the monster now?
她叫你"白痴的那个"
She called you the dumb one.
拜托 她是叫你"白痴的那个"
Uh, she called you the dumb one.
她是发给你的手机 你才是"白痴的那个"
It's your phone, you're the dumb one.
她知道我不会用全大写 是在说你呢
She knows I don't talk in caps, so that's to you.
你才是那个白痴
You're the dumb one.
-炒了她 -要炒自己炒
- Fire her. - No, you fire her.
不要 你来炒
No, you fire her.
我不要 你雇用的人 你自己炒
No, you hired her, you fire her.
我想雇的是大奶茉莉
I wanted to go with Molly big boobs.
她就会准时 一边奶子挂好四椅子准备走了
She'd be here right now with four chairs on each boob.
为什么你不炒她啊
Why can't you just fire her?
很明显她就是叫你白痴
It's clear she called you the dumb one.
行行行 我知道她叫我"白痴的那个"
All right, fine, I know she called me the dumb one.
但我就是不能炒她
But I can't fire her.
我想炒 但我有个障碍
I want to, but there is a block.
在这里
Right here.
它会浮上来 说"不行"
It comes up, and then goes, "nope!"
然后它就继续潜水
It goes right back down.
我不应该是炒人的那个
I am not supposed to fire someone.
我应该是当被人炒的那个
I am the someone who's supposed to be fired.
看来老板得我当了
So I guess I'm the boss, then.
这可以 我去我妈的笼子里等你
Sounds like a plan. I'll be in my mom's cage.
行 那滚过来 你个下层工人
All right, come on, you lowly worker.
帮忙老板把椅子拉出去
Help the boss pull these chairs out.
少对我嚷嚷了 老板 我有"障碍"
Don't yell at me, boss. I'm blocked.
后悔没听我的去灌肠 清"障碍"了吧
Wish you had your enemas now, don't you?
它们跟过来了 我们落入陷阱了
They followed us! We walked into a trap!
这是鼠辈的复仇
It's a vendetta!
我真不敢相信
Ugh, I can't believe this!
我们的实习生在喝鸡尾酒
Our intern's out having cocktails
而我们被困在鼠山鼠海中
and I'm trapped on top of rat mountain!
他来找我报仇了
He's coming after me!
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
麦克斯 救我
Max! Help!
不行 你们这些鼠辈 离她远点
No, you bastards! Get off her!
滚远点
Get off!
我的脚卡在这东西下了
My foot's caught under this thing!
麦克斯 你太猛了
Max, that was amazing.
你单手把那大铁闸给举起了
You just lifted that giant thing up with one hand.
我知道
I know.
现在老娘要炒了那小贱人
And now I'm gonna fire that bitch!
哇 你贴东西也好烂
Wow. You suck at this too.
抱歉我来迟了
Sorry I'm late.
我做梦梦到了我睡过头
I was having a dream that I was sleeping in,
醒来之后 才发现真睡过头了
then I woke up, and I was.
谁是老板
Who's the boss?
托尼·丹扎
Tony Danza?
不 麦克斯 谁才是老板
No, Max, who's the boss?
我才是
I am.
露丝 请坐
Have a seat, Ruth.
这吗
Here?
聪明的选择
Good call.
除了是一个老板
In addition to being a boss,
我也是个女服务员
I am also a waitress.
但当我在工作时 我从不叫人白痴
But when I do my job, I don't call people dumb.
好吧 我是有叫人白痴 但我是当面叫
All right, I do, but at least it's to their face.
你在说那件事啊
Oh, you're talking about that thing?
我叫的是卡洛琳啦
I meant Caroline.
不 我知道你是说我
No, I know you meant me,
因为我不是白痴 卡洛琳也不白痴
Because I'm not dumb and neither is Caroline.
而做生意我学到的一件事就是
And one thing I figured out is that in business,
有时候我得更铁石心肠[无露丝]
maybe I have to be a little more Ruthless.
也就是没有露丝 你被炒了
Meaning no more Ruth. You're fired.
所以我弄不到大学学分了吗
So, I'm not getting college credit?
我大概又要被踢出学校了
I'll probably get kicked out of school again,
不过没事啦 对吧
But no worries, right?
你站出来为自己说话 我真以你为荣
I'm really proud of how you stuck up for yourself.
你也被炒了 抱歉 停不住了
You're fired. Sorry, I can't stop.
你看 麦克斯
Look, Max.
离梦想越来越近了
We're on our way.